

wojciechpalacz.pl

wojciechpalacz@gmail.com

github.com/wPLcz

linkedin.com/wojciech-palacz

+48 531 988 322

Tools/Technologies

FRONTEND CODE:

- HTML
- CSS/SCSS
- SVG
- JAVASCRIPT

FRAMEWORKS/LIBRARIES

- REACT.JS
- MOMENT.JS
- D3.IS
- GSAP
- JQUERY
- BOOTSTRAP BASIC

TOOLS

- WEBSTORM
- VISUAL STUDIO CODE
- PHOTOSHOP
- AFFINITY DESIGNER

OTHER SKILLS

- MOBILE FIRST APPROACH
- RWD: MEDIA QUERIES
- VSC: GIT
- CSS STYLE GUIDE: BEM
- W3C STANDARDS

Wojciech Palacz

JUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

About Me

I work for Citi Europe where I'm responsible for funds reconciliation and valuation. It's great place with multiple areas to discover however after 7 years spent within same department I feel strong need to challenge myself as never before.

Handling multiple Citi internal projects, I felt really great cooperating with IT support department and I believe that is primary source of my idea for business change. After attending few online HTML, CSS, JS tutorials I decided to face serious course and that's how I started at Coders Lab. After over 7 months of tough learn process while I had to match my primary job duties, family duties I had to learn after hours many times sacrificing sleep time. I still find it extremely interesting and worth spending another hours on learning. I believe I'll be able to switch now my primary job, so I can take it full time.

Projects Developed

1. PORTFOLIO WEBSITE

wojciechpalacz.pl

Inspired by multiple websites I decided to show my skills and gain area for my self-development. I used vanilla JS as well as SCSS, but the plan is to reinvent it using React.js. It will contain much more fireworks of course as this needs to be more challenging.

2. NBP USD/PLN live chart github.com/wPLcz/P3-D3.js-JS-SASS

Final project for Coders Lab course. My intention was to work with fetch and SVG elements. Idea that connects these both technologies was pretty obvious. I had to use some API using fetch and visualize it using D3.js. As I wanted to practice with SVG it was excellent scenario for course end. I had to deal with multiple problems & challenges as I wanted to get the job done well. I'm very satisfied with the final result as everything looks smooth and flawless.

3. AD SERVICE

github.com/wPLcz/P1-jQuery-SASS

Simple web service as the result of my jQuery & SCSS homework during Coders Lab course. Used some new CSS hover animations and quite a lot of jQuery code.

Education

2017 - 2018 CODERS LABReact.js weekly course

2006 - 2011 KOŹMIŃSKI UNIVERSITY

MAJOR: Management and Marketing with specialization: Accounting (master's degree)

Languages

English LCCI-2

4. SIMPLE LANDING PAGE

github.com/wPLcz/P2-JS-SASS

Inspired by United Canvas I decided to reproduce some of their solutions. Some techniques have been used later on mine own portfolio website. Website uses SCSS and pure JS.

5. SVG FIRST TOUCH

github.com/wPLcz/SVG1

Results of my first practice with GSAP JS library. My intention was to practice most of the basic movements / effects with SVG stroke elements usage.

6. SVG SECOND TOUCH

github.com/wPLcz/SVG2

I fell in love with all GSAP animations, it combines possibilities provided by CSS but also gives a possibility to play on multiple parts at once or sequentially. It's very simple for basic usage but also extremely complex for advanced techniques. I try to regularly expand my SVG portfolio so feel free to check mine most recent works!

Work History

September 2015 – Onwards SECURITIES JUNIOR ANALYST at Citi Bank

March 2014 – September 2015 SECURITIES SENIOR SPECIALIST at Citi Bank

May 2011 – February 2014 SECURITIES SPECIALIST at Citi Bank

July 2010

TRAINEE AT THE CORPORATE BANKING at Kredyt Bank

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z Ustawą z dnia 29.08.1997 roku o Ochronie Danych Osobowych; tekst jednolity: Dz. U. 2016 r. poz. 922).